hey everyone welcome back to our Channel
I am back with another interesting topic
in the Tosca automation playlist in this
session I am going to tell you how you
can archive your execution logs in the
execution list now we have already seen
how we can execute our test case using
an execution list so the results are
always maintained in the execution lists
which are nothing but the logs which are
stored in the actual log right now for
example this execution list has got an
actual log which is storing the logs as
we go ahead and execute this multiple
times right so multiple execution
entries will be uh stored here as we go
ahead and execute this and everything is
stored in this actual log
so this particular execution list has
got one execution entry and this was
executed uh three months back okay so
this is all fine but what if you are
working on different releases which
happens quarterly or which happens
monthly or which happens weekly now for
each release you need to execute this
test cases again and again right because
these are regression test cases and you
want to test whether your changes in the
application have not affected your
regression test cases
and you want the latest results to be
linked to your requirements so that your
release dashboard can show that these
are the current results okay but for in
order to do that we need to delete our
previous execution logs okay because
these are all logs and although we would
like to keep it but we don't want to
show these logs in our release dashboard
right which is nothing but our
requirements and this execution list
they are linked to the requirements so
if you don't clear this log then it is
going to reflect it in the requirement
section right so one way is to just
clear this logs and it will delete this
Old Log you cannot see this anymore okay
so that you can do easily by right
clicking on actual log and then clicking
on clear lock so that will basically
delete this
but I don't want to do that right
because what I want to do is I want to
compare my results which is my current
results versus my previous results
so I want a way to store my previous
results and also I want the log to have
the current results and that I can do
only by archiving my previous locks so
that I have it in a safe place and I can
always get it back okay
so how you can do that
um that you can do from the execution
list okay so right click on the
execution list and there you will find
and archive actual execution log option
okay so click on that it will ask you
for a archive name so I'm going to give
it RC okay and
rc01 or something
and then I'm going to click ok
it is going to ask you whether you want
to discard your actual log okay
now if you want to remove uh the entries
from the actual log then click on yes if
you don't want to remove then click on
no okay for my case I would click on yes
because I want to remove my actual
entries from the actual log okay
so I'll click on yes and that will clear
off my current actual log so for this
execution entry you don't see any logs
but you only see the archive log with
this particular name okay
um and the actual log is actually empty
now okay it only contains the archive
logs for this execution list
now
um how I can get it back okay uh
so I can just if I want to get this back
into my actual log then I just drag it
and I drop it into the actual log okay
so that way again you will see the
actual log is green that means the
actual log is still present okay
so but I don't want to do that
um so what I will do I will delete this
and I will repeat the process just to
show it one more time so I'm going to
Archive the actual execution log
um and I'm going to this time name it
something like archive
results
okay I am going to discard all the
entries so the actual log is empty now
okay and we have got the archived
results now I can go ahead and execute
this okay
although this time it's going to fail
um that is because
um I have not opened the web page which
it is expecting so this will fail but
that's fine uh I just want to show you
how you can archive your previous looks
and then you can get your latest logs
for that particular execution list so
that your requirement dashboard or your
overall dashboard depicts the current
picture of your test cases not the
previous results okay
also another benefit is you will always
have the previous results with you okay
so you can easily revert this results
back as I showed you just drag and drop
it into the actual log
and that will revert back the results uh
plus you can also see what failed okay
which depth field uh which was passing
previously so from the archived results
I can see that this step had passed
earlier and now this step is failing so
I can easily make out what has changed
in the application and I can debug it
much easier rather than if I would have
just deleted this right
so this way you can maintain an archive
of different results for your execution
list and this is mostly helpful when
you're working with different releases
that's all for this particular video if
you have any questions then please leave
it in the comments
if you like this video then please
subscribe to our Channel
thanks for watching and I will see you
in the next video